webmaster-directory.org 2009-12-12

# Privacy Policy of Webmaster Directory

### Privacy Policy

The Web Master Directory feels powerfully that your information and privileges must be sheltered. To this end, we have organized the following privacy policy to guarantee all measures are taken to protect the interests of our visitors and provide more agreeable site knowledge.

Personal Information

* The Web Master Directory is the sole proprietor of information together on the website, www.webmaster-directory.org

* The Web Master Directory collects and uses individual in a variety of ways including submission forms, registration, and emails.

* The information composed is used for exact business purposes and is not sold or circulated to any third parties. It is used only for the purposes which the visitor anticipated. The main exception to this policy would be if information were requisite to be dispersed to any law enforcement person or agency as required by local laws.

* Payment information is processed through a third party credit card processor and is not collected by The Web Master Directory. This processor does not share, sell or otherwise use personal information for secondary purposes.

* Information is stored in user profiles. We do not use computer generated information, to inquire about extra individual information.

* All individual information is sheltered and used only by those utilizing the information for the particular trade reason.

* On the other hand we share collective information such as page views, browsers, unique visits and other extensive information with our partners and advertisers. No personal information is shared.

* If a user’s information should modify, such as email address, phone number or the user desires to unsubscribe from the service, the user is able to make these changes on the website by contacting us.

Website Communications

Users will only be sent communications by option, and those wishing to unsubscribe from any communications can do so by contacting us frankly.

Website Security

We do our supreme best to guard our website from illicit or unprincipled breaches in security. We take benefit of every gauge available to protect our users’ personal information online. Please write to us for any extra questions on information security.

Third Parties

The Web Master Directory contains associations to other websites including submitted sites and advertisers. We monitor these websites as much as possible to look after the interest of our visitors. Yet we are not in charge for the privacy of visitors or the use of collected information on these websites. We strongly encourage users to read the privacy policies on any website visited.

Policy Changes  
Any changes to the privacy policy will be posted within this deed as well as on the homepage and any other applicable location. It is significant to us that our users be aware of any and all policies concerning the policies for compilation and use of their information. Information will be used in the way under which it was initially composed.

Our privacy policy extends only to this website, www.webmaster-directory.org
